import { Quiz } from '../../types';

const HobbiesQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    description: 'Opakujte v angličtině',
    name: 'Koničky',
    questions: [
      {
        answer: ['play piano'],
        question: 'hrát na klavír'
      },
      {
        answer: ['animals'],
        question: 'zvířata'
      },
      {
        answer: ['collection'],
        question: 'sbírka'
      },
      {
        answer: ['dance'],
        question: 'tanec'
      },
      {
        answer: ['club', 'group', 'circle'],
        question: 'kroužek'
      },
      {
        answer: ['a while', 'a moment', 'moment'],
        question: 'chvíle'
      },
      {
        answer: ['competition'],
        question: 'soutěž'
      },
      {
        answer: ['collect'],
        question: 'sbírat'
      },
      {
        answer: ['gym'],
        question: 'tělocvična'
      },
      {
        answer: ['board games'],
        question: 'stolní hry'
      },
      {
        answer: ['exercise', 'practice', 'drill'],
        question: 'cvičit'
      },
      {
        answer: ['veterinarian', 'vet'],
        question: 'veterinář'
      },
      {
        answer: ['to get married', 'marry'],
        question: 'vdát se'
      },
      {
        answer: ['I enjoy', 'enjoy'],
        question: 'baví mě'
      },
      {
        answer: ['cottage'],
        question: 'chata'
      },
      {
        answer: ['pick mushrooms'],
        question: 'sbírat houby'
      },
      {
        answer: ['traveling', 'travel'],
        question: 'cestování'
      },
      {
        answer: ['currently'],
        question: 'v současné době'
      },
      {
        answer: ['rest', 'relax'],
        question: 'odpočívat'
      },
      {
        answer: ['learn'],
        question: 'učit se'
      },
      {
        answer: ['meet friends'],
        question: 'setkávat se s přáteli'
      },
      {
        answer: ['wedding'],
        question: 'svatba'
      },
      {
        answer: ['hobby'],
        question: 'koníček'
      },
      {
        answer: ['turtle'],
        question: 'želva'
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default HobbiesQuiz;
